ueidaq.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Aerospace, Energy, Defense Data Acquisition & Control | United Electronic Industries

## UEI Privacy Statement

Your right to privacy is a priority to us at United Electronic Industries. We recognize your need for reasonable control of information that you share with UEI. Therefore, this statement is a corporate-wide guideline and is not limited to our online business. We do not sell your information to outside organizations. Our goal in gathering information is to consistently improve our relationship with you, our customer. We use the following guidelines to protect the information we collect during your visit to our website, www.ueidaq.com; over the telephone; at trade shows; or through any other interaction. Because these guidelines affect information about you, please read them carefully and contact us if you have any questions or concerns.

**Information UEI gathers online**

Every time you visit www.ueidaq.com, we automatically collect information such as your IP address (the Internet address of your computer), the locale, language, country, your screen resolution, and the browser you are using, the Web page from which you came. This information is general and currently not tied directly to your name, or user profile I identification number. The information is gathered instead across multiple users to build a statistical analysis of the site, so that we can learn, from this information, more about trends in traffic patterns and site use, so we can improve the website for our users. There are some areas of our site, where you will be asked to provide additional personal information for specific purposes, such as billing and shipping information required for online ordering, or for software download registration. You only need to provide this information to us once, by creating an user profile. This information might include your name, e-mail address, company information, mailing address, application information, product preferences, or contact preferences.

**Use of the collected user information and data**

This information remains confidential. With the information you volunteer, we can process your purchases, confirm your orders, notify you of updates to our site and products, and provide you with specific product and local event information. We add any information you provide to our customer database. Information added to our customer database is aggregated with other information previously collected. Without your prior consent you will not receive periodic mailings, e-mails, or telephone calls from us about new products and services, discounts, special promotions, or upcoming events. At any time, you can change the personal information we have stored in our customer database or request not to be contacted for marketing activities. Email the request to unsubscribe to [enews@ueidaq.com](mailto:enews@ueidaq.com).

**UEI uses of cookies**

A cookie is a small file, typically only a few bytes, placed on your computer’s hard drive. If you agree, then your browser adds the text in a small file. At UEI, we primarily use cookies identify you as a user, and maintain your status on the website during your visit. By associating a small unique ID number in the cookie file accepted by your browser, our website is then able to “remember” information about your preferences, by matching the ID of the cookie placed on your computer, with the ID associated with your profile in our database. The only data we have associated with that cookie is data that you have provided in your user profile. _We do not store any personal information in the cookies we place on your computer_. This practice is strictly enforced. In talking with many of our customers, we believe that the benefit we both gain from proper use of cookies is worthwhile. 

**Use of Google Analytics**

Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies or IP-adress to help the website analyze how users use the site, to monitor and analyze use of our services. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information on our behalf for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity, and providing us other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The IP-address that your browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

**Your information is secure with UEI**

We have invested time and resources to ensure that our online and internal security procedures help safeguard your information. When you see either a solid key icon or a locked padlock icon at the lower portion of your browser window, your connection with our site is secured through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). _Learn more about our online security measures at[Wikipedia.org](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer)_. We use industry-standard encryption technologies, such as SSL, when transferring and receiving your personal information on our site. Pages requesting personal information should always have one of these icons. If you do not see one of these icons, please contact UEI to complete your transaction over the phone. Credit card information is only used for processing payment and is not used for other purposes. If you do not feel comfortable submitting your payment information online, we do offer a print and fax purchasing option by which you can print the contents of your shopping cart and fax your order to us. Please call customer service for more information (508) 921-4600

**Information is never shared with third parties**

To keep your information confidential, UEI does not release your personal information, except as we describe below or as required by law. Your information is never shared or sold for the purposes of any third party use. We only use the personal information we collect to support and develop your relationship with UEI.

**Release of Information**

UEI does reserve the right to release any information about you to protect our systems or business. Also, we can release personal information when we have reason to believe you to be in violation of our current or later website Terms of Use or other published guidelines, or have reason to believe you to have initiated or participated in any illegal activity. We can release this information without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order in response to court and governmental orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests, and other legal requirements.

**Third-party website links**

Any links to third-party websites are provided on [www.ueidaq.com](http://www.ueidaq.com/).
